The Magic of Ordinary Days is a drama, romance, tv
movie film directed by Brent Shields.
Pregnant out of wedlock, an educated young woman is pressured by her father into an
arranged marriage with a lonely farmer in this drama set during WWII.
Livy, played by Keri Russell.
Ray Singleton, played by Skeet Ulrich.
Martha, played by Mare Winningham.
Florence, played by Tania Gunadi.
Walter, played by Eric Winter.
Rose, played by Gwendoline Yeo.
The Magic of Ordinary Days is a Hallmark Hall of Fame production based on a novel of the
same name by Ann Howard Creel and adapted as a teleplay by Camille Thomasson.
It was directed by Brent Shields, produced by Andrew Gottlieb and
stars Keri Russell, Skeet Ulrich, and Mare Winningham.
The film first aired on CBS on January 30, 2005, and received an encore
broadcast on the same network exactly five years later.
The tone is emotional.